{
    "subject": "Maria_Christina_of_Austria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Alfonso_XII_of_Spain",
    "human_readable": "Maria Christina of Austria is married to Alfonso XII of Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9495476484298706,
            "question": "Who is Maria Christina of Austria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9230265021324158,
            "question": "How did the marriage between Maria Christina and Alfonso XII impact Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9198055267333984,
            "question": "Who was Alfonso XII of Spain married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8764063715934753,
            "question": "What is the name of the Spanish king who is married to Maria Christina of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8439989686012268,
            "question": "Were there any significant events during Maria Christina and Alfonso XII's marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.804399847984314,
            "question": "Was Alfonso XII of Spain's wife from a different country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6794716119766235,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Maria Christina of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3739044666290283,
            "question": "To which royal family does Maria Christina belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22664685547351837,
            "question": "What were some of Alfonso XII's accomplishments as king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03673531860113144,
            "question": "Can you name any other royal couples throughout history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maria Christina of Austria is married to Alfonso XII of Spain.",
            "html": "yago_28776_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Alfonso XII's accomplishments as king?",
            "html": "yago_28776_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family does Maria Christina belong?",
            "html": "yago_28776_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Maria Christina of Austria?",
            "html": "yago_28776_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28776_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that Archduchess Maria Christina (also referred to as Maria Cristina) was indeed married to King Alfonso XII of Spain. This is supported by multiple entries in the provided context, which detail their marriage and royal connections."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}